Guide to the David Starr Jordan Papers SC0058
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Correspondence, Series I
  - General Correspondence, 1872-1931; Series I-A
    - 1909, Dec 20-31, and undated (Box 65, Folder 628)
    - 1910, January 1-10 (Box 66, Folder 629)
    - 1910, January 11-20 (Box 66, Folder 630)
    - 1910, Jan 21-31, and undated (Box 66, Folder 631)
    - 1910, February 1-10 (Box 66, Folder 632)
    - 1910, February 11-20 (Box 66, Folder 633)
    - 1910, Feb 21-28, and undated (Box 66, Folder 634)
    - 1910, March 1-10 (Box 66, Folder 635)
    - 1910, March 11-20 (Box 66, Folder 636)
    - 1910, March 21-25 (Box 66, Folder 637)
    - 1910, Mar 26-31, and undated (Box 67, Folder 638)
    - 1910, April 1-8 (Box 67, Folder 639)
    - 1910, April 9-16 (Box 67, Folder 640)
    - 1910, April 17-24 (Box 67, Folder 641)
    - 1910, Apr 25-30, and undated (Box 67, Folder 642)
    - 1910, May 1-8 (Box 67, Folder 643)
    - 1910, May 9-16 (Box 67, Folder 644)
    - 1910, May 17-24 (Box 67, Folder 645)
    - 1910, May 25-31, and undated (Box 67, Folder 646)
    - 1910, June 1-10 (Box 67, Folder 647)
    - 1910, June 11-20 (Box 68, Folder 648)
    - 1910, Jun 21-30, and undated (Box 68, Folder 649)
    - 1910, July 1-10 (Box 68, Folder 650)
    - 1910, July 11-20 (Box 68, Folder 651)
    - 1910, Jul 21-31, and undated (Box 68, Folder 652)
    - 1910, Aug 1-31, and undated (Box 68, Folder 653)
    - 1910, September 1-20 (Box 68, Folder 654)
    - 1910, Sep ember 21-30, and undated (Box 68, Folder 655)
    - 1910, October 1-10 (Box 68, Folder 656)
    - 1910, October 11-20 (Box 69, Folder 657)
    - 1910, October 21-27 (Box 69, Folder 658)
    - 1910, Oct 28-31, and undated (Box 69, Folder 659)
    - 1910, November 1-6 (Box 69, Folder 660)
    - 1910, November 7-16 (Box 69, Folder 661)
    - 1910, Nov 17-30, and undated (Box 69, Folder 662)
    - 1910, Dec 1-31, and undated (Box 69, Folder 663)
    - 1911, January 1-10 (Box 70, Folder 664)
    - 1911, January 11-20 (Box 70, Folder 665)
    - 1911, January 21-28 (Box 70, Folder 666)
    - 1911, Jan 29-31, and undated (Box 70, Folder 667)
    - 1911, February 1-4 (Box 70, Folder 668)
    - 1911, February 5-7 (Box 70, Folder 669)
    - 1911, February 10-14 (Box 70, Folder 670)
    - 1911, February 15-19 (Box 71, Folder 671)
    - 1911, February 20-24 (Box 71, Folder 672)
    - 1911, Feb 25-28, and undated (Box 71, Folder 673)
    - 1911, March 1-5 (Box 71, Folder 674)
    - 1911, March 6-8 (Box 71, Folder 675)
    - 1911, March 9-12 (Box 71, Folder 676)
    - 1911, March 13-16 (Box 71, Folder 677)
    - 1911, March 17-20 (Box 71, Folder 678)
    - 1911, March 21-25 (Box 72, Folder 679)
    - 1911, Mar 26-31, and undated (Box 72, Folder 680)
    - 1911, April 1-6 (Box 72, Folder 681)
    - 1911, April 7-13 (Box 72, Folder 682)
    - 1911, April 14-20 (Box 72, Folder 683)
    - 1911, April 21-25 (Box 72, Folder 684)
    - 1911, Apr 26-30 and undated (Box 72, Folder 685)
    - 1911, May 1-6 (Box 72, Folder 686)
    - 1911, May 7-14 (Box 73, Folder 687)
    - 1911, May 15-18 (Box 73, Folder 688)
    - 1911, May 19-25 (Box 73, Folder 689)
    - 1911, May 26-31, and undated (Box 73, Folder 690)
    - 1911, June 1-13 (Box 73, Folder 691)
    - 1911, June 14-19 (Box 73, Folder 692)
    - 1911, Jun 20-30, and undated (Box 73, Folder 693)
    - 1911, July 1-15 (Box 73, Folder 694)
    - 1911, July 16-23 (Box 74, Folder 695)
    - 1911, July 24-28 (Box 74, Folder 696)
    - 1911, Jul 29-31, and undated (Box 74, Folder 697)
    - 1911, August 1-8 (Box 74, Folder 698)
    - 1911, August 9-22 (Box 74, Folder 699)
    - 1911, Aug 23-31, and undated (Box 74, Folder 700)
    - 1911, September 1-9 (Box 74, Folder 701)
    - 1911, September 10-19 (Box 74, Folder 702)
    - 1911, Sep ember 20-30, and undated (Box 74, Folder 703)
    - 1911, October 1-12 (Box 75, Folder 704)
    - 1911, October 13-25 (Box 75, Folder 705)
    - 1911, Oct 26-31, and undated (Box 75, Folder 706)
    - 1911, November 1-3 (Box 75, Folder 707)
    - 1911, November 4-13 (Box 75, Folder 708)
    - 1911, November 14-23 (Box 75, Folder 709)
    - 1911, Nov 24-31, and undated (Box 75, Folder 710)
    - 1911, December 1-12 (Box 76, Folder 711)
    - 1911, December 13-26 (Box 76, Folder 712)
    - 1911, Dec 27-31, and undated (Box 76, Folder 713)
    - 1912, January 1-5 (Box 76, Folder 714)
    - 1912, January 6-10 (Box 76, Folder 715)
    - 1912, January 11-15 (Box 76, Folder 716)
    - 1912, January 16-20 (Box 77, Folder 717)
    - 1912, January 21-26 (Box 77, Folder 718)
    - 1912, Jan 27-31, and undated (Box 77, Folder 719)
    - 1912, February 1-6 (Box 77, Folder 720)
    - 1912, February 7-11 (Box 77, Folder 721)
    - 1912, February 12-15 (Box 77, Folder 722)
    - 1912, February 16-19 (Box 78, Folder 723)
    - 1912, February 20-25 (Box 78, Folder 724)
    - 1912, Feb 26-29, and undated (Box 78, Folder 725)
    - 1912, March 1-5 (Box 78, Folder 726)
    - 1912, March 6-11 (Box 78, Folder 727)
    - 1912, March 11-16 (Box 78, Folder 728)
    - 1912, March 17-22 (Box 79, Folder 729)
    - 1912, March 23-29 (Box 79, Folder 730)
    - 1912, Mar 30-31, and undated (Box 79, Folder 731)
    - 1912, April 1-7 (Box 79, Folder 732)
    - 1912, April 8-11 (Box 79, Folder 733)
    - 1912, April 12-17 (Box 79, Folder 734)
    - 1912, April 18-23 (Box 79, Folder 735)
    - 1912, Apr 24-30, and undated (Box 80, Folder 736)
    - 1912, May 1-8 (Box 80, Folder 737)
    - 1912, May 9-14 (Box 80, Folder 738)
    - 1912, May 15-22 (Box 80, Folder 739)
    - 1912, May 23-31, and undated (Box 80, Folder 740)
    - 1912, June 1-11 (Box 80, Folder 741)
    - 1912, June 12-18 (Box 81, Folder 742)
    - 1912, Jun 19-30, and undated (Box 81, Folder 743)
    - 1912, July 1-10 (Box 81, Folder 744)
    - 1912, July 11-24 (Box 81, Folder 745)
    - 1912, Jul 25-31, and undated (Box 81, Folder 746)
    - 1912, August 1-9 (Box 81, Folder 747)
    - 1912, August 10-22 (Box 81, Folder 748)
    - 1912, Aug 23-31, and undated (Box 82, Folder 749)
    - 1912, September 1-8 (Box 82, Folder 750)
    - 1912, September 9-13 (Box 82, Folder 751)
    - 1912, September 14-20 (Box 82, Folder 752)
    - 1912, September 21-26 (Box 82, Folder 753)
    - 1912, Sep ember 27-31, and undated (Box 82, Folder 754)
    - 1912, October 1-6 (Box 83, Folder 755)
    - 1912, October 9-12 (Box 83, Folder 756)
    - 1912, October 14-20 (Box 83, Folder 757)
    - 1912, October 21-27 (Box 83, Folder 758)
    - 1912, Oct 28-31, and undated (Box 83, Folder 759)
    - 1912, November 1-8 (Box 83, Folder 760)
    - 1912, November 9-16 (Box 84, Folder 761)
    - 1912, November 17-24 (Box 84, Folder 762)
    - 1912, Nov 25-30, and undated (Box 84, Folder 763)
    - 1912, December 1-6 (Box 84, Folder 764)
    - 1912, December 7-12 (Box 84, Folder 765)
    - 1912, December 13-19 (Box 84, Folder 766)
    - 1912, December 20-26 (Box 84, Folder 767)
    - 1912, Dec 27-31, and undated (Box 85, Folder 768)
    - 1913, January 1-6 (Box 85, Folder 769)
    - 1913, January 7-10 (Box 85, Folder 770)
    - 1913, January 11-16 (Box 85, Folder 771)
    - 1913, January 17-21 (Box 86, Folder 772)
    - 1913, January 22-28 (Box 86, Folder 773)
    - 1913, Jan 29-31, and undated (Box 86, Folder 774)
    - 1913, February 1-6 (Box 86, Folder 775)
    - 1913, February 7-11 (Box 86, Folder 776)
    - 1913, February 12-16 (Box 86, Folder 777)
    - 1913, February 17-21 (Box 87, Folder 778)
    - 1913, Feb 22-28, and undated (Box 87, Folder 779)
    - 1913, March 1-5 (Box 87, Folder 780)
    - 1913, March 6-12 (Box 87, Folder 781)
    - 1913, March 13-20 (Box 87, Folder 782)
    - 1913, March 21-26 (Box 88, Folder 783)
    - 1913, Mar 27-31, and undated (Box 88, Folder 784)
    - 1913, April 1-7 (Box 88, Folder 785)
    - 1913, April 8-14 (Box 88, Folder 786)
    - 1913, April 15-22 (Box 88, Folder 787)
    - 1913, Apr 23-30, and undated (Box 88, Folder 788)
    - 1913, May 1-7 (Box 89, Folder 789)
    - 1913, May 8-12 (Box 89, Folder 790)
    - 1913, May 13-16 (Box 89, Folder 791)
    - 1913, May 17-21 (Box 89, Folder 792)
    - 1913, May 22-26 (Box 89, Folder 793)
    - 1913, May 27-31, and undated (Box 89, Folder 794)
    - 1913, June 1-12 (Box 90, Folder 795)
    - 1913, June 13-30 (Box 90, Folder 796)
    - 1913, July (Box 90, Folder 797)
    - 1913, August (Box 90, Folder 798)
    - 1913, September (Box 90, Folder 799)
    - 1913, October (Box 90, Folder 800)
    - 1913, November (Box 90, Folder 801)
    - 1913, December (Box 90, Folder 802)
    - 1914, January (Box 90, Folder 803)
    - 1914, February (Box 90, Folder 804)
    - 1914, March (Box 91, Folder 805)
    - 1914, April (Box 91, Folder 806)
    - 1914, May (Box 91, Folder 807)
    - 1914, June (Box 91, Folder 808)
    - 1914, July (Box 91, Folder 809)
    - 1914, August (Box 91, Folder 810)
    - 1914, September (Box 91, Folder 811)
    - 1914, October 1-12 (Box 91, Folder 812)
    - 1914, October 13-22 (Box 91, Folder 813)
    - 1914, Oct 23-31, and undated (Box 92, Folder 814)
    - 1914, November (Box 92, Folder 815)
    - 1914, December (Box 92, Folder 816)
    - 1915, January (Box 92, Folder 817)
    - 1915, February (Box 92, Folder 818)
    - 1915, March (Box 92, Folder 819)
    - 1915, April (Box 92, Folder 820)
    - 1915, May (Box 92, Folder 821)
    - 1915, June (Box 92, Folder 822)
    - 1915, July (Box 92, Folder 823)
    - 1915, August (Box 92, Folder 824)
    - 1915, September (Box 93, Folder 825)
    - 1915, October (Box 93, Folder 826)
    - 1915, November (Box 93, Folder 827)
    - 1915, December (Box 93, Folder 828)
    - 1916, January (Box 93, Folder 829)
    - 1916, February (Box 93, Folder 830)
    - 1916, March (Box 93, Folder 831)
    - 1916, April (Box 93, Folder 832)
    - 1916, May (Box 93, Folder 833)
    - 1916, June (Box 94, Folder 834)
    - 1916, July (Box 94, Folder 835)
    - 1916, August (Box 94, Folder 836)
    - 1916, September (Box 94, Folder 837)
    - 1916, October (Box 94, Folder 838)
    - 1916, November (Box 94, Folder 839)
    - 1916, December (Box 94, Folder 840)
    - 1917, January (Box 94, Folder 841)
    - 1917, February (Box 94, Folder 842)
    - 1917, March (Box 94, Folder 843)
    - 1917, April (Box 94, Folder 844)
    - 1917, May (Box 95, Folder 845)
    - 1917, June (Box 95, Folder 846)
    - 1917, July (Box 95, Folder 847)
    - 1917, August (Box 95, Folder 848)
    - 1917, September (Box 95, Folder 849)
    - 1917, October (Box 95, Folder 850)
    - 1917, November (Box 95, Folder 851)
    - 1917, December (Box 95, Folder 852)
    - 1918, January (Box 95, Folder 853)
    - 1918, February (Box 95, Folder 854)
    - 1918, March (Box 95, Folder 855)
    - 1918, April (Box 95, Folder 856)
    - 1918, May (Box 96, Folder 857)
    - 1918, June (Box 96, Folder 858)
    - 1918, July (Box 96, Folder 859)
    - 1918, August (Box 96, Folder 860)
    - 1918, September (Box 96, Folder 861)
    - 1918, October (Box 96, Folder 862)
    - 1918, November (Box 96, Folder 863)
    - 1918, December (Box 97, Folder 864)
    - 1919, January (Box 97, Folder 865)
    - 1919, February (Box 97, Folder 866)
    - 1919, March (Box 97, Folder 867)
    - 1919, April (Box 97, Folder 868)
    - 1919, May (Box 97, Folder 869)
    - 1919, June (Box 98, Folder 870)
    - 1919, July (Box 98, Folder 871)
    - 1919, August (Box 98, Folder 872)
    - 1919, September (Box 98, Folder 873)
    - 1919, October (Box 98, Folder 874)
    - 1919, November (Box 99, Folder 875)
    - 1919, December (Box 99, Folder 876)
    - 1920, January (Box 99, Folder 877)
    - 1920, February (Box 99, Folder 878)
    - 1920, March (Box 99, Folder 879)
    - 1920, April (Box 99, Folder 880)
    - 1920, May (Box 100, Folder 881)
    - 1920, June (Box 100, Folder 882)
    - 1920, July (Box 100, Folder 883)
    - 1920, August (Box 100, Folder 884)
    - 1920, September (Box 100, Folder 885)
    - 1920, October (Box 100, Folder 886)
    - 1920, November 1-15 (Box 100, Folder 887)
    - 1920, November 16-30 (Box 100, Folder 888)
    - 1920, December 1-16 (Box 101, Folder 889)
    - 1920, December 17-31 (Box 101, Folder 890)
    - 1921, January 1-15 (Box 101, Folder 891)
    - 1921, Jan 16-31, and undated (Box 101, Folder 892)
    - 1921, February (Box 101, Folder 893)
    - 1921, March (Box 102, Folder 894)
    - 1921, April (Box 102, Folder 895)
    - 1921, May (Box 102, Folder 896)
    - 1921, June (Box 102, Folder 897)
    - 1921, July (Box 102, Folder 898)
    - 1921, August (Box 102, Folder 899)
    - 1921, September (Box 102, Folder 900)
    - 1921, October (Box 103, Folder 901)
    - 1921, November (Box 103, Folder 902)
    - 1921, December 1-19 (Box 103, Folder 903)
    - 1921, Dec 20-31, and undated (Box 103, Folder 904)
    - 1922, January 1-17 (Box 103, Folder 905)
    - 1922, January 18-31 (Box 104, Folder 906)
    - 1922, February 1-14 (Box 104, Folder 907)
    - 1922, February 15-29 (Box 104, Folder 908)
    - 1922, March (Box 104, Folder 909)
    - 1922, April 1-14 (Box 104, Folder 910)
    - 1922, April 15-29 (Box 104, Folder 911)
    - 1922, May 1-19 (Box 105, Folder 912)
    - 1922, May 20-31 (Box 105, Folder 913)
    - 1922, June (Box 105, Folder 914)
    - 1922, July (Box 105, Folder 915)
    - 1922, August (Box 105, Folder 916)
    - 1922, September (Box 105, Folder 917)
    - 1922, October (Box 106, Folder 918)
    - 1922, November (Box 106, Folder 919)
    - 1922, December (Box 106, Folder 920)
    - 1923, January 1-18 (Box 106, Folder 921)
    - 1923, January 19-31 (Box 106, Folder 922)
    - 1923, February 1-18 (Box 106, Folder 923)
    - 1923, February 19-31 (Box 107, Folder 924)
    - 1923, March 1-8 (Box 107, Folder 925)
    - 1923, March 9-20 (Box 107, Folder 926)
    - 1923, March 21-31 (Box 107, Folder 927)
    - 1923, April 1-12 (Box 107, Folder 928)
    - 1923, April 13-30 (Box 107, Folder 929)
    - 1923, May 1-15 (Box 108, Folder 930)
    - 1923, May 16-31 (Box 108, Folder 931)
    - 1923, June 1-17 (Box 108, Folder 932)
    - 1923, June 18-31 (Box 108, Folder 933)
    - 1923, July 1-17 (Box 108, Folder 934)
    - 1923, July 18-31 (Box 108, Folder 935)
    - 1923, August 1-14 (Box 109, Folder 936)
    - 1923, August 15-22 (Box 109, Folder 937)
    - 1923, Aug 23-31, and undated (Box 109, Folder 938)
    - 1923, September 1-15 (Box 109, Folder 939)
    - 1923, September 16-30 (Box 109, Folder 940)
    - 1923, October 1-15 (Box 109, Folder 941)
    - 1923, October 16-31 (Box 110, Folder 942)
    - 1923, November 1-8 (Box 110, Folder 943)
    - 1923, November 9-21 (Box 110, Folder 944)
    - 1923, November 22-30 (Box 110, Folder 945)
    - 1923, December 1-15 (Box 110, Folder 946)
    - 1923, December 16-31 (Box 110, Folder 947)
    - 1924, January 1-8 (Box 111, Folder 948)
    - 1924, January 9-20 (Box 111, Folder 949)
    - 1924, January 21-31 (Box 111, Folder 950)
    - 1924, February 1-14 (Box 111, Folder 951)
    - 1924, February 15-29 (Box 111, Folder 952)
    - 1924, March 1-13 (Box 111, Folder 953)
    - 1924, March 14-22 (Box 111, Folder 954)
    - 1924, March 23-31 (Box 112, Folder 955)
    - 1924, April 1-10 (Box 112, Folder 956)
    - 1924, April 11-20 (Box 112, Folder 957)
    - 1924, April 21-30 (Box 112, Folder 958)
    - 1924, May 1-18 (Box 112, Folder 959)
    - 1924, May 19-31 (Box 112, Folder 960)
    - 1924, June 1-13 (Box 112, Folder 961)
    - 1924, June 14-30 (Box 113, Folder 962)
    - 1924, July 1-16 (Box 113, Folder 963)
    - 1924, July 17-31 (Box 113, Folder 964)
    - 1924, August (Box 113, Folder 965)
    - 1924, September 1-15 (Box 113, Folder 966)
    - 1924, September 16-30 (Box 113, Folder 967)
    - 1924, October 1-13 (Box 113, Folder 968)
    - 1924, October 14-31 (Box 114, Folder 969)
    - 1924, November 1-18 (Box 114, Folder 970)
    - 1924, November 19-31 (Box 114, Folder 971)
    - 1924, December 1-9 (Box 114, Folder 972)
    - 1924, December 10-17 (Box 114, Folder 973)
    - 1924, December 18-31 (Box 114, Folder 974)
    - 1925, January (Box 114, Folder 975)
    - 1925, February (Box 115, Folder 976)
    - 1925, March 1-22 (Box 115, Folder 977)
    - 1925, March 23-31 (Box 115, Folder 978)
    - 1925, April (Box 115, Folder 979)
    - 1925, May (Box 115, Folder 980)
    - 1925, June 1-16 (Box 115, Folder 981)
    - 1925, June 17-30 (Box 115, Folder 982)
    - 1925, July 1-19 (Box 116, Folder 983)
    - 1925, July 20-31 (Box 116, Folder 984)
    - 1925, August 1-17 (Box 116, Folder 985)
    - 1925, August 18-31 (Box 116, Folder 986)
    - 1925, September (Box 116, Folder 987)
    - 1925, October (Box 116, Folder 988)
    - 1925, November (Box 116, Folder 989)
    - 1925, December (Box 117, Folder 990)
    - 1926, January (Box 117, Folder 991)
    - 1926, February (Box 117, Folder 992)
    - 1926, March (Box 117, Folder 993)
    - 1926, April (Box 117, Folder 994)
    - 1926, May (Box 117, Folder 995)
    - 1926, June (Box 117, Folder 996)
    - 1926, July (Box 117, Folder 997)
    - 1926, August (Box 117, Folder 998)
    - 1926, September (Box 117, Folder 999)
    - 1926, October (Box 117, Folder 1000)
    - 1926, November (Box 117, Folder 1001)
    - 1926, December (Box 118, Folder 1002)
    - 1927, Janaury 1-16 (Box 118, Folder 1003)
    - 1927, January 17-31 (Box 118, Folder 1004)
    - 1927, February (Box 118, Folder 1005)
    - 1927, March (Box 118, Folder 1006)
    - 1927, April (Box 118, Folder 1007)
    - 1927, May 1-14 (Box 118, Folder 1008)
    - 1927, May 15-31, and undated (Box 118, Folder 1009)
    - 1927, June (Box 119, Folder 1010)
    - 1927, July (Box 119, Folder 1011)
    - 1927, August (Box 119, Folder 1012)
    - 1927, September (Box 119, Folder 1013)
    - 1927, October (Box 119, Folder 1014)
    - 1927, November (Box 120, Folder 1015)
    - 1927, December (Box 120, Folder 1016)
    - 1928, January (Box 120, Folder 1017)
    - 1928, February (Box 120, Folder 1018)
    - 1928, March (Box 120, Folder 1019)
    - 1928, April (Box 120, Folder 1020)
    - 1928, May (Box 120, Folder 1021)
    - 1928, June (Box 120, Folder 1022)
    - 1928, July (Box 121, Folder 1023)
    - 1928, August (Box 121, Folder 1024)
    - 1928, September (Box 121, Folder 1025)
    - 1928, October (Box 121, Folder 1026)
    - 1928, November (Box 121, Folder 1027)
    - 1928, December (Box 121, Folder 1028)
    - 1929, January (Box 121, Folder 1029)
    - 1929, February (Box 122, Folder 1030)
    - 1929, March (Box 122, Folder 1031)
    - 1929, April (Box 122, Folder 1032)
    - 1929, May (Box 122, Folder 1033)
    - 1929, June (Box 122, Folder 1034)
    - 1929, July (Box 122, Folder 1035)
    - 1929, August (Box 122, Folder 1036)
    - 1929, September (Box 122, Folder 1037)
    - 1929, October (Box 122, Folder 1038)
    - 1929, November (Box 123, Folder 1039)
    - 1929, December (Box 123, Folder 1040)
    - 1930, January (Box 123, Folder 1041)
    - 1930, February (Box 123, Folder 1042)
    - 1930, March (Box 123, Folder 1043)
    - 1930, April (Box 123, Folder 1044)
    - 1930, May (Box 123, Folder 1045)
    - 1930, June (Box 123, Folder 1046)
    - 1930, July (Box 123, Folder 1047)
    - 1930, August (Box 123, Folder 1048)
    - 1930, September (Box 123, Folder 1049)
    - 1930, October (Box 123, Folder 1050)
    - 1930, November (Box 123, Folder 1051)
    - 1930, December (Box 123, Folder 1052)
    - 1931, January (Box 123, Folder 1053)
    - 1931, February (Box 124, Folder 1054)
    - 1931, March (Box 124, Folder 1055)
    - 1931, April (Box 124, Folder 1056)
    - 1931, May (Box 124, Folder 1057)
    - 1931, June (Box 124, Folder 1058)
    - 1931, July (Box 124, Folder 1059)
    - 1931, August (Box 124, Folder 1060)
    - 1931, September (Box 124, Folder 1061)
    - 1931, October-December (Box 124, Folder 1062)
    - A-J, Undated (Box 124, Folder 1063)
    - K-Z, Undated (Box 124, Folder 1064)
    - Addenda, circa 1895-1913 (Box 124, Folder 1065)
    - Letters to Charles H. Rieber, and, Mar 8, 1901 May 16, 1901 (Box 125, Folder 1)
      General note
      Box 125 contains letters added to Series I-A of the Jordan Papers after January 1983, which are included in the index but were not microfilmed.
    - Letter to Miss Berry, with drawings by Jordan. Written aboard the Alameda., Mar 17, 1905 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Letters to George T. Clark, and, Mar 25, 1907 Dec 10, 1909? (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Letter to Clytie Sweet, '21, and poem by DSJ Santa Clara; Virgen y Martir, copied for Clytie Sweet, May 17, 1919 (1893) (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Letters to Dr. Nelson Brayton, and Christmas card to the Braytons and the LaDows, from Jessie Knight Jordan, Jul 17, 1911, undated (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Christmas card to George T. Clark (photograph of DSJ with his dog Jock), 19-Dec-27 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Letter to Joseph L. Bristow (International Congress of Zoology), [photocopy], May 21, 1910 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with World Book Company, 1923-1926 (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - Letter to Edward A. Bryant, May 16, 1923
      - Letter from Whitman Brown (?), 12-Aug-24
      - Letter to Edward A. Bryant, June 3, 1926
      - Letter to Alfred O. Shedd, 25-Sep-26
      - Letter to H. C. Bryant, 25-Sep-26
      - Letter to Alfred A. Shedd, 12-Oct-26
      - Note regarding the printing of fish names, undated
    - Outgoing correspondence, [partially photocopies], 1891-1928 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Letters from Melville Best Anderson, 1913-1914 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Letters from John Casper Branner, 1913-1914 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Letters from V. L. Callogy, J. E. Coover, and William J. Crook, 1913, 1914, 1914 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Leters from George A. Clark, 1914 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Letters from W. H. Carruth, 1914 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Letters from Aurelio Espinosa, 1913-1914 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Letters from A. L. Guinan, A. B. Hitchcock, Herbert Hoover, and Alvin S. Johnson, 1913, 1902, 1914, 1914 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Letter from Tetsuro Hayasaka, in Japanese, circa 1900 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Letters from Emil Hollmann, 1913 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Letters from Timothy Hopkins, 1914 (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Letter from Hachiro Mine, in Japanese, circa 1900 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Letter from Harry C. Peterson, 1914 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Letter from H. Satonura, G. Otsuka, and S. Kondo (S.U. janitors), undated (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Letters from Ray Lyman Wilbur, 1914 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous memos (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Printed poems (Box 125, Folder 25)
  - Letterpress books, 1898-1910; Series I-AA
    - 1898 Mar 30 - 1900 Jun 5, 1898-1900; 1; 1 volume(s) (Box 1)
    - 1900 Sep 27 - 1902 Feb 5; 1906 Feb 1 - 1906 Mar 12, 1900-1906; 2; 1 volume(s) (Box 1)
    - 1900 Nov 23 - 1901 May 2, 1900-1901; 3; 1 volume(s) (Box 2)
    - 1901 May 2 - Oct 11, 4; 1 volume(s) (Box 2)
    - 1901 Oct 9 - 1902 Jan 4, 1901-1902; 5; 1 volume(s) (Box 3)
    - 1902 Jan 4 - Feb 25, 6; 1 volume(s) (Box 3)
    - 1902 Feb 25 - Apr 15, 7; 1 volume(s) (Box 4)
    - 1902 Apr 15 - Jun 11, 8; 1 volume(s) (Box 4)
    - 1902 Jun 11- Sep 19, 9; 1 volume(s) (Box 5)
    - 1902 Sep 19 - Nov 10, 10; 1 volume(s) (Box 5)
    - 1902 Dec 24 - 1903 Feb 6, 1902-1903; 11; 1 volume(s) (Box 6)
    - 1903 Feb 6 - Mar 10, 12; 1 volume(s) (Box 6)
    - 1903 Mar 10 - Apr 17, 13; 1 volume(s) (Box 7)
    - 1903 Apr 17 - May 20, 14; 1 volume(s) (Box 7)
    - 1903 May 20 - Jun 29, 15; 1 volume(s) (Box 8)
    - 1903 Jul 11 - Sep 7, 16; 1 volume(s) (Box 8)
    - 1903 Sep 7 - Oct 27, 17; 1 volume(s) (Box 9)
    - 1903 Oct 27 - Dec 8, 18; 1 volume(s) (Box 9)
    - 1903 Dec 8 - 1904 Jan 29, 1903-1904; 19; 1 volume(s) (Box 10)
    - 1904 Jan 28 - Mar 7, 20; 1 volume(s) (Box 10)
    - 1904 Mar 7 - Jun 1, 21; 1 volume(s) (Box 11)
    - 1904 Jun 1 - Aug 1, 22; 1 volume(s) (Box 11)
    - 1904 Sep 25 - Nov 2, 24; 1 volume(s) (Box 12)
    - 1904 Dec 13 - Jan 22, 1904-1905; 25; 1 volume(s) (Box 12)
    - 1905 Jan 23 - Mar 4, 26; 1 volume(s) (Box 13)